{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820530186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820530186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820531080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820531080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820531734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820531734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820532347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820532347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820532561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820532561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820533304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820533303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" DASARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820539538","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820539538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820540528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820540528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820540626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820540626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820546842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820546842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 3d3c1a43-3bbb-4a4f-ac23-8224baa888a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820566286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820566286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820572139","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820572139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820580529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820580529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820584896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820584895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820590475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820590475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820591561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820591561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820598089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820598089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820604224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820604224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820605446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820605446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820614214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820614214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820617701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820617701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820621728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820621728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hujambo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hu"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820623668","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820623668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hujambo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" hu"," userResponse":" hu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820624606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820624606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hujambo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820631160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820631160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hujambo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820637894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820637894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hujambo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820638877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820638877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hujambo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820643169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820643169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mchicha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820650338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820650337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mchicha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820656936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820656935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mchicha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820657935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820657935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mchicha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820658927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820658927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mchicha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820662339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820662339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820668132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820668132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820669012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820669012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820669876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820669876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820673203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820673202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukuta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820673781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820673781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukuta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820674679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820674679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukuta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820678688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820678687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820678893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820678893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndo"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820685005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820685004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ndo"," userResponse":" ndo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820686312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820686312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820697551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820697551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204152"," gameId":" 2e687056-1445-4dd0-b15a-7af7794c9041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}